Guide to the The Good Fight: The Abraham Lincoln Brigade in the Spanish Civil War: Audiotapes ALBA.AUDIO.216
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
The Good Fight: The Abraham Lincoln Brigade in the Spanish Civil War: Audiotapes
1937-1988
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Sills, Sam
ALBA.AUDIO.216
10 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons, 5 flat boxes, 1 manuscript box, and 1 CD box
The Good Fight, a feature-length documentary film released in 1983, pays homage to American volunteers who served with the International Brigades during the Spanish Civil War. The Good Fight: The Abraham Lincoln Brigade in the Spanish Civil War: Audiotapes (1937-1988) includes audio recordings of interviews, events, narration, radio broadcasts, and other audio used in the production of the film.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Good Fight: the Abraham Lincoln Brigade in the Spanish Civil War: Production Materials was donated to Abraham Lincoln Brigade Archives in 1983 by filmmakers Noel Buchner, Mary Dore and Sam Sills. This collection came to New York University in January 2001 as part of the original acquisition of ALBA collections, formerly housed at Brandeis University.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into three series:
Series I. Interviews
Series II. Event Recordings
Series III. Source Audio
Historical Note
The Good Fight, a feature-length documentary film released in 1983, pays homage to American volunteers who served with the International Brigades during the Spanish Civil War. The film is an exploration of the political motives that compelled the volunteers to travel to Spain in the 1930s, their weathering of anti-communist sentiment during the 1940s and 50s, and their political engagement in later life. The film makes extensive use of archival footage from the war, stills, primary documents, radio broadcasts, newsreels, and interviews. With the help of an NEH grant, filmmakers Noel Buchner, Mary Dore and Sam Sills interviewed more than 125 combat and medical veterans in the course of researching and editing the film. The final documentary, which is narrated by Studs Terkel, features eleven veterans including Bill Bailey, Steve Nelson, Milt Wolff, Edward Balchowsky, Salaria Kee (a.k.a. Salaria Kea) O'Reilly and Evelyn Hutchins.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to some audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Audiovisual materials that have not been preserved may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Tamiment Library and Wagner Labor Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596, with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Contents
The Good Fight: The Abraham Lincoln Brigade in the Spanish Civil War: Audiotapes (1937-1988) includes audio recordings of "pre-interviews" with volunteers, most of whom were later interviewed on film; event recordings, including Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade National Conferences, group meetings, and memorials; and other audio recordings used in the production of the film, such as Studs Terkel's narration, radio broadcasts, musical recordings, speeches, and sound samples.
This collection includes interviews across multiple audio formats for some interviewees; it is unclear whether these are separate interviews or duplicative content.
Related Materials
ALBA 216: The Good Fight: the Abraham Lincoln Brigade in the Spanish Civil War: Production Materials
ALBA FILM 216: The Good Fight: The Abraham Lincoln Brigade in the Spanish Civil War: Film Materials
ALBA PHOTO 216: The Good Fight: The Abraham Lincoln Brigade in the Spanish Civil War: Photographs
Spanish Civil War, Spain, 1936-1939; Spain -- History -- Civil War, 1936-1939 -- International brigades.; Spain -- History -- Civil War, 1936-1939 -- Veterans.; Documentary films
- Series I. Interviews, 1979-1988; 10 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons, 5 flat boxes,1 manuscript box, and 1 CD box
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically by the interviewee's last name.
  Scope and Contents
  Series I. Interviews (1979-1988) includes interviews and "pre-interviews" with volunteers, most of whom were later interviewed on film. This series includes interviews across multiple audio formats for some interviewees; it is unclear whether these are separate interviews or duplicative content.
  - Frank Alexander, circa 1980-1983; cuid43204
    - Tape 1, cuid44908 (Box 10, Audiocassette 216-341)
    - Tape 2, cuid44909 (Box 10, Audiocassette 216-342)
    - Tape 3, cuid44910 (Box 10, Audiocassette 216-343)
    - Tape 4 (Box 10, Audiocassette 216-350)
      Based on the label, this tape may be a duplicate of 216-342.
  - Joseph Azar, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_346)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_347)
  - Ed Balchowsky, circa 1980-1983
    - #1 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_039)
    - #2 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_040)
  - Bill Bailey, September 15, 1981 - January 19, 1983
    - #1, September 15, 1981 (Box Shared Tamiment 204, Quarter inch audio reel 216_021)
    - #2, September 15, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_022)
    - #3, September, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_023)
    - #4, September, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_024)
    - #5, September 16, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_025)
    - #6, September 16, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_026)
    - #7, September 16, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_027)
    - #8, September, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_028)
    - #9, September, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_029)
    - #10, September 18, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_030)
    - #11, September 18, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_031)
    - #12, September 18, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_032)
    - II #2, undated (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_092)
      Related Materials
      For part one of this interview, see reel 216_091.
    - II #3, undated (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_093)
    - II #4, undated (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_094)
    - II #5, undated (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_095)
    - III, January 17, 1983 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 216_215)
    - III, January 17-18, 983 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 216_216)
    - III, January 18, 1983 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 216_217)
    - III, January 18-19, 1983 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 216_218)
    - III, January 19, 1983 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 216_219)
    - III, January 19, 1983 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 216_220)
    - Audio recording, undated (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_277)
    - Audio recording, undated (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_278)
    - Audio recording, undated (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_279)
    - Audio recording, undated (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_280)
  - Hilda Bell Roberts, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_288)
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_289)
  - Ed Bender, circa 1980-1983 (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_287)
  - Alvah Bessie, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_264)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_265)
  - Ester Silverstein Blanc, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_267)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_268)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_393)
  - Lou Bortz, circa 1980-1983 (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_309)
  - George Brodsky, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_249)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_250)
  - Archie Brown, May 10, 1988
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_284)
    - Access CD (Box Shared Tamiment 115, Cd 216_284)
  - Paul Burns, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_364)
    - Audio recording (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_365)
  - Albert Edward Chisholm, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_333)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_334)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_335)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_336)
  - Tedd Cogswell, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_352)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_353)
  - Milt Cohen, circa 1980-1983 (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_314)
  - Robert Colodny, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_307)
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_308)
  - Maury Colow, circa 1980-1983 (Box Shared Tamiment 168, Audiocassette 216_391)
  - B. Colow, circa 1980-1983 (Box Shared Tamiment 168, Audiocassette 216_392)
  - Jerry Cook, April 5, 1979
    - Audio recording, April 5, 1979 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_176)
    - Audio recording, April 5, 1979 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_177)
    - Audio recording, April 5, 1979 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_178)
    - Audio recording, April 5, 1979 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_179)
    - Audio recording, April 5, 1979 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_180)
    - Audio recording, April 5, 1979 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_181)
      Also includes Weisman.
  - Rudy Corbin, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_292)
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_293)
  - James Crooks, circa 1980-1983 (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_338)
  - Ruth Davidow, circa 1980-1983
    - #1 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_001)
    - #2 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_002)
    - #3 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_003)
    - #4 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_004)
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_289)
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_290)
  - Tony DeMaio, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_356)
    - Audio recording (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_357)
  - Lini DeVries, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_347)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_348)
  - Becky Durem, circa 1980-1983 (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_294)
  - Muriel and Richard Eldridge, June, 1988 (Box Shared Tamiment 115)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    No analog original present for this access CD.
    Interviewed by Carlos Gonzalez.
  - Max Farrar, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_344)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_345)
  - Ralph Fasanella, circa 1980-1983
    - #1 (Box Shared Tamiment 204, Quarter inch audio reel 216_153)
    - #2, Pete Smith #1 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_154)
  - Harry Fisher and John Rody, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_257)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_258)
    - Audio recording (Box 8)
  - Moe Fishman, April 4, 1979 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_175)
  - Irving Frankel, circa 1980-1983 (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_303)
  - Bill Gandall, May, 1988 (Box Shared Tamiment 115)
    2 discs total. No analog original present.
  - Carl Geiser, circa 1980-1983
    - #2 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_169)
      For part one of this interview, see reel 216_168.
    - #3 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_170)
    - #4 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_171)
  - Henry Giler, circa 1980-1983 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_172)
  - Robert Gladnick, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_327)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_328)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_329)
  - Howard Goddard, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_281)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_282)
  - Irving Goff, circa 1980-1983
    - #1 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_099)
    - #2 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_100)
    - #3 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_101)
    - #4 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_102)
    - #5 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_103)
    - #6 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_104)
  - Irving Gold, circa 1980-1983 (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_346)
  - Butch Goldstein, September 29, 1981 - March 23, 1982
    - #1, September 29, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_049)
    - #2, September 29, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_050)
    - #3, September 30, 1981 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_051)
    - #4, September 30, 1981 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_052)
    - #5, September 30, 1981 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_053)
    - #6, September 30, 1981 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_054)
    - #7, Abe Osheroff #1, September 30, 1981 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_055)
    - #1, March 23, 1982 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_079)
    - #2, March 23, 1982 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_080)
    - #3, March 23, 1982 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_081)
    - #4, March 23, 1982 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_082)
    - #5, March 23, 1982 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_083)
    - #6, March 23, 1982 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_084)
    - #1, undated (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_119)
    - #2, undated (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_120)
    - #3, undated (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_121)
  - Sam Gonshak, 1981
    - Audio recording (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_362)
    - Audio recording (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_363)
  - Ken Graeber, circa 1980-1983
    - #1 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_125)
    - #2 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_126)
    - #3 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_127)
  - Jack Hartzman and May Hartzman, circa 1980-1983 (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_302)
  - Manny Harriman, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_296)
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_297)
  - Joe Hautaniemi, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_248)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_249)
  - Gus Heisler and Ray Marantz, circa 1980-1983
    - #2 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_132)
      For part one of this interview, see reel 216_131.
    - #3 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_133)
  - Hemingway, circa 1980-1983 (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_373)
  - Ben Holtzman, September 2, 1980
    - #1 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_203)
    - #2 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 216_204)
    - #3 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 216_205)
    - #4 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 216_206)
    - Audio recording, circa 1980-1983 (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_389)
    - Audio recording, circa 1980-1983 (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_390)
  - John Houseman, circa 1980-1983
    - #1 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_078)
  - Oscar Hunter, circa 1980-1983
    - #1 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_149)
    - #2 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_150)
    - #3 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_151)
    - #4 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_152)
  - Evelyn Hutchins, September 2 - 26, 1981
    - #1, September 26, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_041)
    - #2, September 26, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_042)
    - #3, September 26, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_043)
    - #4, September 26, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_045)
    - #5, September 26, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_044)
    - #6, September 26, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_046)
    - #7, September 26, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_047)
    - #8, September 26, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_048)
    - #1, undated (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_198)
    - #2, undated (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_199)
    - #3, September 2, 1980 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_200)
    - #4, undated (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_201)
    - #5, undated (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_202)
  - Ben Iceland, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_252)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_253)
  - Robert Ingalls and Brooke Carmichael, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_339)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_341)
  - Toby Jensky, circa 1980-1983 (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_351)
  - Sid Kaufman and Duncan Keir, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_304)
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_305)
  - George Kaye, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_280)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_281)
  - Admiral "Kil" Kilpatrick, circa 1980-1983 (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_313)
  - Leonard Lamb, circa 1980-1983
    - #2 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_158)
      For part one of this interview, see reel 216_157.
    - #3 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_159)
    - #4 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_160)
  - Art Landis, circa 1980-1983
    - #1 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_173)
    - #2, Al Tanz #1 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_174)
  - Ed Lending, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_329)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_330)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_331)
  - Rose Leopold, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 115)
    A note on the disc says, "Original tape says 'Rose Leopold' but Courtney thinks it is Malbin / Polishuk."
  - Leonard Levenson, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_353)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_254)
  - Sid Linn, circa 1980-1983 (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_325)
  - Tom Lloyd, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_259)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_260)
  - Vaughn Love, circa 1980-1983; cuid43083
    - Cassette 1, cuid44920 (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_360)
    - Cassette 2, cuid44922 (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_340)
    - Cassette 1 (duplicate), cuid44921 (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_361)
  - Don MacCleod, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_263)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_264)
  - Seema Matlin Goddard, circa 1980-1983 (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_282)
  - Matti Mattson, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_256)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_257)
  - Bill McCarthy, 1981
    - #1, Demonstration #2, September 19, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_033)
    - #2, September 19, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_034)
    - #3, September 19, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_035)
    - #4, September 19, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_036)
    - #5, September 19, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_037)
    - #6, September 19, 1981 (Box 1, Quarter inch audio reel 216_038)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_273)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_274)
  - Luchell McDaniel, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_271)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_272)
  - Art Munday, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_355)
    - Audio recording (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_356)
  - Virginia Malbin, circa 1980-1983 (Box Shared Tamiment 115)
    Interview by Sandy Polishuk.
    12 CDs total. No analog originals present for these access CDs.
  - Carl Marzoni, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_358)
    - Audio recording (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_359)
  - Curly Mende, circa 1980-1983 (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_285)
  - Bill Miller, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_349)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_351)
  - Irving Mitchel, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_297)
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_298)
  - Sidney Narris, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_315)
    - Audio recording (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_316)
  - Steve Nelson, circa 1980-1983
    - #1 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_067)
    - #2 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_068)
    - #3 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_069)
    - #4 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_070)
    - #5 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_071)
  - Harry Nobel, circa 1980-1983
    - #1 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_161)
    - #2 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_162)
    - #3 (Box 4, Quarter inch audio reel 216_163)
  - Marion Noble, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_321)
    - Audio recording (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_322)
  - Charlie Nusser, 1980
    - Audio recording (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_371)
    - Audio recording (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_372)
  - Charles O'Flanerty, circa 1980-1983
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_261)
    - Audio recording (Box 8, Audiocassette 216_262)
  - Pat O'Reilly, circa 1980-1983 (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_311)
  - Salaria Kea O'Reilly, circa 1980-1983; cuid44918
    - Reel 1, cuid45215 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_062)
      Duration: 24 minutes
    - Reel 2, cuid45216 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_063)
      Duration: 25 minutes
    - Reel 3, cuid45217 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_064)
    - Reel 4, cuid45218 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_065)
    - Reel 5, cuid45219 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_066)
      Duration: 21 minutes
    - Cassette 1, cuid36858 (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_310)
      Existence and Location of Copies
      A copy of this interview is also available in ALBA 226; see audiocassettes 226-059 and 226-061.
    - Cassette 2, cuid44919 (Box 9, Audiocassette 216_311)
  - Abe Osheroff, circa 1980-1983
    - #2, October 4, 1981 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_056)
      For part one of this interview, see reel 216_055.
    - #3, October 4, 1981 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_057)
    - #4, October 4, 1981 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_058)
    - #5, October 4, 1981 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_059)
    - #6, October 4, 1981 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_060)
    - #7, October 4, 1981 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_061)
    - #1, undated (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_072)
    - #2, undated (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_073)
    - #3, undated (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_074)
    - #4, undated (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_075)
    - #5, undated (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_076)
    - #6, undated (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_077)
    - #1, undated (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_105)
    - #2, undated (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_106)
    - #3, undated (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_107)
    - #4, Isadore Tivin and Fred Keller #1, undated (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_108)
  - Thomas Page, June 23, 1982
    - #1, June 23, 1982 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_096)
    - #2, June 23, 1982 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_097)
    - #3, June 23, 1982 (Box 2, Quarter inch audio reel 216_098)
    - Audio recording, undated (Box 10, Audiocassette 216_336)
    - Audio recording, undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_367)
    - Audio recording, undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_369)
    - Audio recording, undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 216_370)
  - Al Prago, circa 1980-1983
    - #1 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_128)
    - #2 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_129)
    - #3 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_130)
    - #4, Gus Heisler and Ray Marantz #1 (Box 3, Quarter inch audio reel 216_131)